Guide to the New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records, 1922-2004.
New York State College of Human Ecology. Alumni Affairs and Development Office records
- Stroman, Ann Gustafson, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Strombeck, Helen, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 116)
- Struck, Barbara Medland, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Stull, Carolyn, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 117)
- Stutz, Sarah Purdum, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Stycos, Aglaea Grammen GR (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Styles, Barbara, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Suchman, J. Richard GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Suchet, Bonnie, 1963 (Box 11)
- Suci, George (Box 8, Folder 118)
- Suits, Diane Stewart, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Summer, Frances Hornsby, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Swan, Mary, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 119)
- Swani, Vimla PhD, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Swanson, Virginia Keeler, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Sweeny, Mary GR (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Sweet, Elizabeth M. (Box 8, Folder 120)
- Swift, Marjorie, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 130)
- Swift, Mildred GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Swigert, Jeanne Carnahan, 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Swinton, Frances, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Symons, Mary Anne E. GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Synder, Janet B., 1941 (Box 8, Folder 91)
- Tabor, Rhoda Morris, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Tack, Elizabeth L. (Box 8, Folder 131)
- Tackbary, Helen E., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Taggart, Kathleen GR (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Taietz, Philip PhD, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 132)
- Talpey, Elizabeth Alden, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Tanger, Katrina S., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Tanneberger, Agnes (Box 8, Folder 133)
- Tanner, Michael, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 134)
- Tariant, Barbara, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Tate, Elizabeth, 1938 (Box 8, Folder 135)
- Taylor, Carrie Williams (Box 8, Folder 136)
- Taylor, Dorothy, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Taylor, Gail K. (Box 8, Folder 139)
- Taylor, Janet, 1935 (Box 8, Folder 137)
- Taylor, Portia, 1933 (Box 8, Folder 138)
- Taylor, Wayne A., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 140)
- Tengel, Patricia, 1964 (Box 11)
- Terry, Nancy, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Thalman, Marqaret Morse, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Thastesen, Joan, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Thatcher, June, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Theis, Ruth McBride, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Theophilus, Florence (Box 8, Folder 141)
- Thielker, Shirley, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Thomas, Isabelle, 1930 (Box 8, Folder 142)
- Thomas, Sarah E. GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Thompsett, Marjorie Smith, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Thompson, Betty (Box 8, Folder 143)
- Thompson, Eunice, 1945 (Box 8, Folder 149)
- Thompson, Eunice Bueg, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Thorington, Shirley, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 144)
- Thurm, Emily Gail, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 145)
- Tiedemein, Doris Johnson, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Tillenberg, Joan, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Tindall, Anthony Edward, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 146)
- Tipping, Agnes Hansen, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Titus, Gene Buchanan, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Toan, Eleanore Reed, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Tobie, Josephine M, 1948 (Box 8, Folder 150)
- Tobkin, Elaine, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Todt, Joyce, 1926 (Box 8, Folder 147)
- Tohn, Helen, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Toleman, Dorothy Schmitt, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Toliver, Barbara Bond GR (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Tomkins, Linda Jean Quick, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Tompkins, Elizabeth, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Tompkins, Frances E. GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Tompkins, Helene M. (Box 8, Folder 148)
- Tompkins, Rita Kennedy, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Torance, Phoebe, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Torres, Carmen Celivista GR (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Tortorello, Scott, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 151)
- Tossi, Dhimitra, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Towner, Kathryn Beebe, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Townsend, Anne, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 66)
- Townsend, Carol Gehrka, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Traver, Janet, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- True, Virgina (Box 8, Folder 152)
- Tschirner, Rachel Johnson, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Tucker, Ann B., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Turner, Gloria P., 1982 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Turner, Margaret, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Turner, Margaret Stack, 191 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Turner, Page, 2004 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Turrel, Eloise, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Tuthill, Ruth Humphrey, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Tuttle, Carol Insley, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Twitchell, Janet Perrine, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Twyman, Edna Haussman, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Tyler, Virginia Oakes (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Udall, Dorothy K. (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Udell,Helen, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Ullrich, Caroline Bayne, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Underberg, Joyce Wisbaum, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Underwood, Adelaide, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Unger, Grace, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Unger, Margaret Diebold, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Unger, Roy A & S, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Unterzuber, Barbara Smith, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Urcloart, Doris GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Urquhart, Doris E. (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Usher, Carolyn B., 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Utermolen, Virginia Sr. (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Utter, Nannette Gravener Criss, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Uyeno, Phyllis Stevenson, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Vail, Charlotte Dredger, 1935 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Van Allen, Mary Louise Alstein, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Van Atta, Ruth G. (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Van Bortel, Dorothy BS, MS, 1936, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Van Doren, Irene, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Van Geluwe, Marion Pallace, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Van Ness, Dorotha, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Van Slyke, Virginia (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Van Waganen, Margaret A., 1934 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Van Zandt, Edna, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Vandervort, Helen Bull, 1926 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Vandervort, John, 1923 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- VanTyne, Evelyn, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- VanVleet, Dorothy, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Vatter, Ethel (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Vaughan, Corinne Hickox, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Vaughan, Valerie, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Veeder, James, 1942 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Veeder, Leslie, 1942 (Box 11)
- Venable, Mrs. Regis Illston (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Verbsky,Elizabelth Collins, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Vick, Sara, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Vickery, Ann Winters, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Vieser, Susan Stolp, 1964 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Viewig, Dorothea GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Vikre, Elizabeth Rogalsky, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Vincent, Annette Ms, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Vinski, Helen J., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Visnyei, Prof. Kathryn (Box 9, Folder 28)
- Vogel, Joan, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Vorhis, Hariet Cross, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Vosburg, Joanne R., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Vosburg, Karen, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 30)
- Voss, Carrie King, 1917 (Box 9, Folder 31)
- Vreeland, Virginia, 1932 (Box 9, Folder 29)
- Waddell, Majorie Stee GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Wadleck, Clara, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Wagenhals, Elizabeth Hughes, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Wagner, Wilma, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Wagstaff, Florence (Box 9, Folder 32)
- Wait, Beverly MacNamara, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Wald, Susan, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 33)
- Waldron, Margaret, 1950 (Box 9, Folder 34)
- Waldron, Margaret Gehlert, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Walke, Carl (Box 9, Folder 39)
- Walker, Florence (Box 9, Folder 35)
- Walker, Janet L., 1965 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Walker, Kathryn PhD, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 36)
- Wallaca, Pauline, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Wallace Dorothea, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 37)
- Wallace, Alice Rees, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Waller, Lillian Perhamus, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Waln, Reta, 1931 (Box 9, Folder 38)
- Walsh, Erva, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Walsh, Ruth M., 1941 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Walzer, Dorothy, 1941 (Box 9, Folder 40)
- Ward, Alice MS, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 41)
- Ward, Barbara, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Ward, Frances, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Ward, Janet (Box 9, Folder 42)
- Ward, Linda M., 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Ward, Virginia, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Ware, Bennie Maye GR (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Warn, Hermione, 1928 (Box 9, Folder 43)
- Warnock, Marie Reese, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Warren, Jean (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Washburn, Helen P. GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Waskey, Roth, 1939 (Box 11)
- Waters, Cynthia Heister, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Waters, Martin III, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 45)
- Waverly, Beverly J. GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Way, Hilda and Walter D., 1919 (Box 9, Folder 46)
- Weaver, Alga D. (Box 9, Folder 47)
- Weaver, Gertrude Harvey, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Weaver, Lola (Box 9, Folder 48)
- Weaver, Lola Lackey GR (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Weaver, Sarah Beale, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Webster, Elizabeth Luxford, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Wedell, Marguerite P., 1924 (Box 9, Folder 49)
- Weeks, Barbara, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 50)
- Wehrle, Elizabeth M., 1945 (Box 9, Folder 51)
- Weiner, Grace Gray, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Weiss, Roberta, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Weissman, Jean, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Welch, Muriel Welch, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Weller, Virginia C., 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Wells, Henrietta, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Welter, Doris, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Wender, Carole J., 1961 (Box 2, Folder 67)
- Weng, Virginia, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Werly, Charles M. (Box 9, Folder 52)
- Werly, Jane E. (Box 9, Folder 53)
- Werner, Bamby Snyder, 1952 (Box 9, Folder 54)
- Werst, Ruth, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- West, Dorothy M. GR (Box 9, Folder 55)
- Westlake, Meredith, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Wetherbee, Ann E., 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Whalen, Elsie, 1939 (Box 9, Folder 56)
- Whaley, Barbara (Box 9, Folder 57)
- Wheeler, Phyllis Winkelman (Box 9, Folder 83)
- Whitaker, Alice (Box 9, Folder 58)
- White, Janet C. GR (Box 9, Folder 59)
- White, Marietta N. GR (Box 2, Folder 51)
- White, Mrs. Marjorie Willerton (Box 9, Folder 60)
- White, Nancy, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- White, Ruth Babcock, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Whitlock, Mary Lu De Puy, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Whittemore, Alma (Box 9, Folder 61)
- Whittier, Elinor, 1933 (Box 9, Folder 62)
- Whittier, Mary Ellen, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Wiant, Dorothy, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Widom, Lois Sanow, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Wiegand, Elizabeth (Box 9, Folder 63)
- Wien, Elizabeth, 1963 (Box 9, Folder 64)
- Wierum, Jean, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 65)
- Wierum, Jean Hough, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Wiggans, Dorothy Talbert (Box 9, Folder 66)
- Wilborn, Dorothy M. MS, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Wilcox, Jane Rasmussen, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Wilcox, William Boardman, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 67)
- Wilke, Margaret, 1934 (Box 9, Folder 68)
- Will, Shirley, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Willerton, Helen F., 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Williams, Carolyn Armstrong (Box 2, Folder 73)
- Williams, Cathy Moore, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Williams, Charlene (Box 9, Folder 69)
- Williams, Elizabeth Kandiko, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Williams, Joan, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Williams, Kim Kandiko (Box 9, Folder 70)
- Williams, Margaret, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Williams, Nancy, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Williamson, Lucille (Box 9, Folder 71)
- Williamson, Midred Haslett, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Willis, Gail, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 72)
- Wilson, Amy Hunter (Box 9, Folder 73)
- Wilson, Carolyn, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 74)
- Wilson, Elizabeth (Box 9, Folder 75)
- Wilson, Jane Grep, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Wilson, Joyce, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 76)
- Wilson, Joyce Jarnagin, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Wilson, Phyllis, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Wilson, Phyllis S. Jr., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 78)
- Wilson, Rayma Carter, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Wilson, Rosemary, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 77)
- Wines, Mary E. GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Winter, Vera F.J., 1958 (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Winters, Ellen, 1930 (Box 9, Folder 79)
- Winters, Jayne GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Wishnetsky, Theodore, 1949 (Box 9, Folder 80)
- Witherspoon, Dorothea Bentley, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 81)
- Wizeman, Patricia A., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 82)
- Woehr, Sue, 1965 (Box 9, Folder 84)
- Woehr, Susan Nye, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 71)
- Wolfe, Helen (Box 9, Folder 85)
- Wolff, Elsie, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Wollner, Frances A., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Wolverton, Joan M., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Wood, Francesi, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Wood, John P., 1924 (Box 9, Folder 87)
- Wood, Margaret, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Wood, Mary B. (Box 9, Folder 88)
- Wood, Natalie Fairbanks (Box 9, Folder 89)
- Wood, Sandra Wills, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Woodruff, Alcie Buhsen, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Woods, Carol O., 1941 (Box 9, Folder 86)
- Woods, Carole Ogle, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Woods, Jane, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Woods, Margaret, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 90)
- Woods, Margaret MS, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Woodward, Nancy Ann, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Woolson, Helen Chappell (Box 9, Folder 91)
- Worthington, Carolyn (Box 9, Folder 92)
- Wright, Carol E., 1953 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Wright, E. Truman (Box 9, Folder 95)
- Wright, Eleanor, 1936 (Box 9, Folder 93)
- Wright, Frances, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Wright, Lucille AM, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 94)
- Wu, Sun-I GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Wurts, Alan, 1948 (Box 9, Folder 96)
- Wu-Wang, Olivia GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Yacker, Janet Reese, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Yacowitz, Harold, 1944 (Box 9, Folder 97)
- Yang, Hsien-Tong GR (Box 9, Folder 98)
- Yost, Nancy Lehrboch, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Young, Carol, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Young, Charlotte (Box 9, Folder 99)
- Young, Frances (Box 9, Folder 101)
- Young, Frances E. (Box 9, Folder 100)
- Young, Josephine 0. GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Young, Pauline, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Young, Priscilla, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Zadik, Eleanor M., 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Zaehringer, Mary V. GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Zak, Jean Sprott, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Zamir, Billa GR (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Zehner, Mary, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Zelickman, Evelyn, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Zensen, Margaret S. GR (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Zicht, Anita J., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Ziegel, Ruth Covell, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Zimmerman, Marlea E., 1954 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Zimmerman, Pearl (Box 9, Folder 102)
- Zingerle, Carrie H, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Zubon, Elizabeth, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Zucchelli, Linda, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 68)
- Advancement Committee Meetings, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Advancement Committee Meetings, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Advancement Committee Meetings, 1999-2003 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- MVR Courtyard Project, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- MVR Courtyard Project, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- MVR Courtyard Project, 1999-2000 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Communications Study - Phase I - Alumni Perceptions, May 1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Alumni Survey Interviewer Manual, 1991-02 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Alumni Survey - Data Documentation Donor and Non-Donor Weighted Sample, 1921-1990 (Box 10)
- Alumni Focus Group Research, 2003-01 (Box 10)
- Alumni Survey- Preliminary Data Presentation, 2003-09 (Box 10)
- Alumni Survey, 2003-10 (Box 10)
- Emeritus Brunch, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Urie Bronfenbrenner Symposium, 1994-04 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Senior Reception, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Alumni-in-Residence Program, 1994-10-1994-11 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Alumni-in-Residence Program, 1995-10 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Home Bureau Scholarship Reception, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Donor Recognition, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Hofstra Long Island Event, 1996-03 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Alumni Career Talk, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Bronfenbrenner Talk - New York City, 1997-04 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Endowed Chair-Description, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Mann Library - Honor with Books, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Naming Opportunities for Donors, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Public Affairs Annual Reports, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Public Affairs Annual Report, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Public Affairs- Goals, Objectives, Priorities, 1996-1998 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Dean's Portraits, no date (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Annual Report and Budget, 2002-2003 (Box 10, Folder 26)